<record xmlns="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><header><identifier>doi:10.7910/DVN/OTTBDX</identifier><datestamp>2022-12-05T07:10:46Z</datestamp><setSpec>IQSS</setSpec></header><metadata><oai_dc:dc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:oai_dc="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc/ http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc.xsd"><dc:title>Geocoding of worldwide patent data</dc:title><dc:identifier>https://doi.org/10.7910/DVN/OTTBDX</dc:identifier><dc:creator>Seliger, Florian</dc:creator><dc:creator>Kozak, Jan</dc:creator><dc:creator>de Rassenfosse, Gaétan</dc:creator><dc:publisher>Harvard Dataverse</dc:publisher><dc:description>The file geoc_inv.txt contains identifiers for patent first filings (corresponding to appln_id in PATSTAT), latitude, longitude, city, region, and country of the inventor. Missing coordinates have been imputed from equivalents and other second filings or from information on the location of applicants. The file also contains a variable indicating the source of information ('source'):
1: information comes from the first filing itself
2: information comes from direct equivalent
3: information comes from other subsequent filings
4: information comes from the applicant’s location in first filings
5: information comes from the applicant’s location in the equivalent
6: information comes from the applicant’s location in other subsequent filings;
the column 'coord_source' indicates the source of coordinates (whether they come from geolocalisation services, from geonames, or from PatentsView). 
It is possible to select certain types of first filings based on column 'type'. For example, Paris Convention priority filings can be retrieved by specifying type=priority.
The file geoc_app.txt contains location information of applicants. Sources of information (first filings, equivalents, etc.) are thus browsed in reverse order.
A detailed data description can be found in de Rassenfosse, Kozak, Seliger 2019: Geocoding of worldwide patent data, published in 'Scientific Data' and available at https://doi.org/10.1038/s41597-019-0264-6.

Please note the following: 
The files geoc_inv_person.txt and geoc_app_person.txt contain person IDs for inventors and applicants, respectively, whenever the location information comes from PATSTAT. If not, the person_id is = 0. These files are not described in the paper. They have been made accessible to improve interoperability with PATSTAT data.
Some files had to be zipped in order to upload them to Harvard Dataverse.</dc:description><dc:subject>Business and Management</dc:subject><dc:subject>Social Sciences</dc:subject><dc:subject>Patents</dc:subject><dc:subject>Geocoding</dc:subject><dc:subject>Location of inventors</dc:subject><dc:subject>PATSTAT</dc:subject><dc:date>2019-07-23</dc:date><dc:contributor>Seliger, Florian</dc:contributor></oai_dc:dc></metadata></record>